ACTWU's Social Services Department Records 5619/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- R.D. Burke, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Barnes, Sylvia, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Baily, Walter Lee and Eliza, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Butler, James; Johnson, Larry; Moates, Frank, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Crowe, Virginia and Forrest, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Dillard, Eules, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Dixons, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Dutton, Nadine, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Hall, Julius, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Kohler Strike Support, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Long, Lucille, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Lyda, William Paul, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Patterson, Daris, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Lucille Smith, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Stuan, Lois, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- Thomas, Carrie Workman, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Turner, Caudle, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Whitlock, Hoyt and Jeanette, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 55)
- Williams, Mary Ruth, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Monthly Reports, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 57)
- Monthly Report, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 58)
- Not Made Cases, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 59)
- Not Made Cases, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 60)
- Cases, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 61)
- Cases, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 62)
- Threads Project, Semi-Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 63)
- Threads Project Semi-Annual Report, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 64)
- Threads Project Semi-Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 65)
- Threads Project Semi-Annual Report, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 66)
- New York - Final report, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 67)
- Final Report, Original, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Suppliers and Consultant Check Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Scriptomatic Scriptomaster Address Cards (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Receipts, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Memos to Finance Department, 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- National Endowment for Humanities; Humanities Grant - Outstanding Bills, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Receipts and Deposit Slips, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Request for Advance of Reimbursement, Completed Forms, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Federal Cash Transactions Reports, Blank forms, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Pre-Threads, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Threads, Florida, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Chanukah, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Film Library, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- National Endowment for Humanities Proposal, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Financial Status Reports, Completed, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Letter of Credit, 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Letter of Credit Vouchers, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Financial Status Report Forms, Blank, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Expense Forms, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Federal Cash Transactions Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Threads Financial, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Audit Information, 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 901-925, 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 851-900, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 801-850, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 751-800, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 701-750, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 601-650, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 651-700, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Guest Lecturers - Request for Payment (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 551-600, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 501-550, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 451-500, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 401-450, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 351-400, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 301-351, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 251-300, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 205-250, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 154-204, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Invoices Paid Check No. 101-153, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- New York State Checks No. 101-179, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- National Endowment for Humanities Grant Notebook (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Threads Project Grant, 1979-1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Annual Eastern Summer School, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- National Endowment for Humanities Grant First Proposal, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- New York Council for the Humanities Grant, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Threads Reprint Permissions, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Publicity [1 of 2], 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Publicity [2 of 2], 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Outreach, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Related Projects, 1977-1981 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Related Projects, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Introduction to Threads (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Interns, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Labor History, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Labor History Through Song (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Joyce Miller, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Needlework, 1975-1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Outlines, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Safety Packet, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- New Berry, South Carolina, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- The Triangle Fire (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Work, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Work, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Quilting Package, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Threads Questionnaire (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Threads Language program, Spanish to English (Box 35, Folder 3)
  Spanish and English
- Work - Originals (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Marti-Soy un hombre sincero (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Castillo - Intelectuales apoliticos (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Violeta Parra - Volver a los 17 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Miguel Hernandez - El nino yuntero (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Francisco, El Hombre (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Guillen - El apellido (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hilos - Threads, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  November 8, Spanish and English
- Hilos - Unit 2 - Work syllabus (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Rosa Leon - La Soltera (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Milanes - Para Vivir (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Guillen - Los Dos Abuelos (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Soto - La Cautiva (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Domitila - Childhood (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Upa Negrito (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Julia de Burgos (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Soto - Miniatura (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Guillen - Cancion de Cuna (Box 35, Folder 21)
- J.L. Gonzalez, En el Fondo (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Marti - Mi Caballero (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Rulfo - Es que somos (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Beneditti - Te quiero (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Anon - Carta de amor, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Milaves - todas las cosas que aun nos queden por vivir (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Milaves - Hoy la vi (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Milaves - Llegaster a Mi Cuerpo (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Violeta Parra - Rin Del Angelito (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Domitila - Un dia de una (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Supplemental Reasons - Work, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Session 1 - Work (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Session two - Work (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Session Three - Work (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Session Four - Work (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Session five - Work (Box 35, Folder 37)
- Session six - Work (Box 35, Folder 38)
- Session Seven - Work (Box 35, Folder 39)
- Session eight - Work (Box 35, Folder 40)
- Work Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 41)
- Work Knoxville - Course Materials, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- Poetry (Work), 1965-1977 (Box 35, Folder 43)
- Community: Proposed Humanities Curriculum, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- Thought of Community (Box 35, Folder 45)
- Community: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- Community: Self Made men, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- Community: Rethink Material (Box 35, Folder 48)
- Community: Reading Materials, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 49)
- Family: Our own kind, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- Family: Reading List (Box 35, Folder 51)
- Family: Bel Gropes Article (Box 35, Folder 52)
- Family: Hannah's Daughters, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 53)
- Family: The uncommitted alienated Youth in America, 1960-1977 (Box 35, Folder 54)
- Family: The Politics of Child Rearing (Box 35, Folder 55)
- Family: Family Histories, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 56)
- Family: The Open Door (Box 35, Folder 57)
- Family: The Family, 1971-1978 (Box 35, Folder 58)
- Family: The Black Family, 1971-1976 (Box 35, Folder 59)
- Family: Swapping, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 60)
- California Packet (Box 35, Folder 61)
- Family Poetry, 1960-1979 (Box 35, Folder 62)
- Family: Poetry, 1970-1978 (Box 35, Folder 63)
- Films and Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 64)
- Illinois Women's History Exhibit, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 65)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Senior Center Humanities Program, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 66)
- Humanities Proposal, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 67)
- History, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 68)
- National Endowment for Humanities - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 69)
- National Endowment for Humanities Grant - Names, Numbers, Arrangements, Etc., 1977 (Box 35, Folder 70)
- Humanities Seminar for Labor Leaders, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 71)
- Humanities Arts Council, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Tom Herviman's Proposal (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Women's Play, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- National Endowment for Humanities Grant - Publicity, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Institute on Pluralism and Group Identity, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Massachusetts Foundation for Humanities and Public Policy [1 of 2], 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Massachusetts Foundation for Humanities and Public Policy [2 of 2], 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Current - Humanities, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Expense Records, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Preliminary Proposal Humanities, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Grant Endowment Humanities, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Grant Endowment Humanities, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Other National Endowment for Humanities Projects, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Total Education in the Total Environment, Inc., 1972-1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- JTPK Management Information System, Instructions for Forms, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Zapateros Unidos, Mision: Empleo, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Zapateros Unidos, Mision: Empleo (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Worker Literacy Project, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Mision Empleo: Information, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Immigrants Rights, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Regions, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Worksheets, Secretary Assistance, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Mision/Empleo Bills, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Rose Stationary, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Mision Empleo - Peer Outreach Workshop, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Noemi Torres, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Mision Empleo - Forms, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Margarita Curet, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- MC, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Mision Empleo - Job Services, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Job Club, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Memorandum, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Mision Empleo - Older Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Outreach Counselors, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Restaurants (Box 36, Folder 36)
- Lizardi, Bridget, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Mision Empleo. Participant Enrollment, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Letters and Memo Copies, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Publicity, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- Phone Calls that have been made by Staff, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- Job Skills Seminar, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- Office Supplies, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- Plant Closings, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Copies of Job Order, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Albany Rally, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  January 21
- Unemployment Fund, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Semenarios, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Zapateros Unidos, Mision: Empleo, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 50)
- Mision Empleo: Participant Folder/Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Morales, Felicitia, 1983-1987 (Box 36, Folder 52)
- MIS 3 Data Transmission, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 53)
- Mision Empleo - Manufacturing (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Mision Empleo. Gloversville, New York, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Mision: Empleo, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Toress, Sonia, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Mision Empleo Seminars, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Mission/Empleo: Interviews (Box 37, Folder 3)
- M. Curet - Time Sheets, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Attendance Mision Empleo - Margarita Cuvet and Alejandro Duhalde, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Wm. Guinn and Simek, Hart - Time Sheets, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Mision Empleo - Time Sheets - S. Levine, T. Peil, T. Tyadke, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Staff - Monthly Time Distribution Sheet (Mision Empleo), 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Mission Employment - Match Funds Time Sheets, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Job Match Project (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Hotline Trabajo (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Staff Meeting, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Meeting, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Mision Empleo Correspondence, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Benstein, Mazdalena, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Bustos, William, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Mackenzie, David, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Vidal, Maria, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Mision Empleo. Returned Questionnaires, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Reports, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- New York State Department of Labor Registration Forms, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Serrano, Carmelo, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Word Processing Department (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Aduilar, Mirian, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Ortiz, Jaime, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Ramikissoon, Nateram, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Job Club, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Montes, Juana M., 1987 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Members, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Mision: Empleo "A", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Mision: Empleo "B", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Mision: Empleo "C", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Mision: Empleo "D", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Mision: Empleo "E", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Mision: Empleo "F", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Mision: Empleo "G", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Mision: Empleo "H", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Mision: Empleo "I", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Mision: Empleo "J", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Mision: Empleo "K", 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Mision: Empleo "L", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Mision: Empleo "M", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Mision: Empleo "N", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Mision: Empleo "O", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Mision: Empleo "P", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Mision: Empleo "Q", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Mision: Empleo "R", 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Mision: Empleo "S", 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Mision: Empleo "T", 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Mision: Empleo "U", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Mision: Empleo "V", 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Mision: Empleo "W", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Mision: Empleo "XYZ", 1986 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Job Match: #563 Shoe Repairers, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Shoe #563: Ceta Project, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- T-O-Dey Service Corp: #563S, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Eneslow Shoe Centers #563S, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Job Match Shoe Council #2, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Figueroa, Fernando, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Job match: ALICO Contacts, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Job Match: Outreach, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Original List of Certified Numbers, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Outreach Flier (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Jobmatch: Making Funds Records, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Monthly Reimbursement of Travel Expenses Report, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Emerging Funds, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Jobmatch: Foster Timesheets, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Jobmatch; Secretarial Time-Sheets, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Assistant Project Director, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Bunhen Agent, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Intake Receptionist, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "A-M", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "M-T", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "U-Z", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "A-E", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "F-S", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Mision Empleo, Reach-out Program - Staff Time Sheets "T-Z", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Joseph Lopez, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Camelo Serrano, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Noemi Torres, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Sonia Torres, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Margarita Curet, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Mision Empleo - Staff Time Sheets - Teresa Tyacke, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Mision Empleo - Visitation Log, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Mision Empleo - Telephone Log, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Mision: Empleo - Pautas del Seminario (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Mision: Empleo - Job Finding Skills Workshop, 1979-1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Desk Calender, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, Returned, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  English and Spanish
- Correspondence, Returned [1 of 2], 1987 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, Returned [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Marvin Ciporen Incoming Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Memo Correspondence Incoming, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Marvin Ciporen Incoming Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Marvin Ciporen Outgoing Correspondence, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Victoria Lebovics Outgoing Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Memo Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- National THREADS meeting Outgoing Correspondence, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Memo Correspondence, Outgoing, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Advisory Board Correspondence, Incoming, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Marvin Ciporen Outgoing Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Marvin Ciporen Incoming Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Advisory Board Correspondence, Outgoing, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Advisory Board Meeting Incoming Correspondence, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Advisory Board Meeting Outgoing Correspondence, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Diploma (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Discussion Leaders, 1978-1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Conferences, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Conference Reports, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Victoria Lebovics Outgoing Correspondence, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Victoria Lebovics Incoming Correspondence, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Victoria Lebovics Incoming Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- D.L. Incoming Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Consultants Meeting Outgoing Correspondence, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Victoria Lebovics Incoming Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Victoria Lebovics Outgoing Correspondence, 1980` (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Marvin Ciporen Outgoing Correspondence, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Fall River/New Bedford - Resumes, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Fall River/New Bedford Course Materials - i.e. Poems, songs, stories, flyers etc. (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Hilos Flyer (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Detroit - Threads logs/Reports, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Film and Theater, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- J. Luis Gonzalez - Stories (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Fall River/New Bedford - Reports, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Fall River/New Bedford - Sue Benson Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- San Antonio, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Dominican Republic (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Song Lyrics - P.R. (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Detroit and Erwin - Resource people, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Erwin - Course Materials - i.e. Poems, songs, stories, flyers etc., 1979 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Fall River/New Bedford - Curriculum (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Lawrence/Bread and Roses, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Threads Activities, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- New York Review and Evaluation, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Detroit - Course Materials - i.e. Poems, songs, stories, flyers etc., 1978 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Detroit - Wayne State University and County Community College, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Ewrin - Curriculum, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Erwin - Reports, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Detroit - Miriam Frank incoming Correspondence, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Detroit - Curriculum, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Labor Studies, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- National Endowment for Humanities Grant - Task Force Correspondence, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Transcript - First Meeting, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  May 17
- 2nd Humanities meeting - Task Force Transcript (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Complete Transcript Unedited - 1st Meeting, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Grant Correspondence Bette Craig and Joyce Miller, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Inquires about Threads - Newsletter and Project Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board Summer School, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Southern States Joint Board - Summer School (Box 40, Folder 3)
- New England Joint Board - Summer School, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- New York - Course Materials - i.e. Poems, songs, stories, flyers etc. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- New York - Resumes, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Hudson, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- New York Reports, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Buffalo, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Knoxville - Curriculum, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Knoxville - June and Brenda Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Knoxville - Resource People, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Knoxville - Resumes, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Knoxville Forum - 2001: Expo '82 and Beyond, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Knoxville - Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Los Angeles, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Spanish Language Program, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Endowment for Humanities Grant, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Endowment for Humanities Grant, 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Resumes, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Threads Mailing list (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Next Newsletter (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Film Resources, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Discussion Guide Courses, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Xerox Job Orders, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Missouri Conference on Work, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Detroit - Resumes, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Threads Project Synopsis, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Threads Newsletter Correspondence, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Colors, Shapes, and Memories: Three Folk Artists (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Film Guides, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Threads Guides, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Introductory Guide Book, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Endowment for Humanities Grant Narrative Notes, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Film Guides Original, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Proposed Budget for Humanities Program, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Proposals, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Rehabilitations Sicyling Center, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Rehabilitation and State Commission for the Blind, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Rehabilitation: Veterans Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Rehabilitation: Willowbrook Development Center, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  May 3
- Affirmative Action Employment, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Rehabilitation Services, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Affirmative Action: Case Histories Handicapped, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Affirmative Action: Case Histories Employees, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Affirmative Action Components, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Affirmative Action Components, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Affirmative Action Employment [1 of 2], 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Affirmative Action Employment [2 of 2], 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action Models (Box 41, Folder 7)